<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
	<title>Alex Piotrowski</title>
	<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/categories/</link>
	<description>Recent content in Categories on Alex Piotrowski</description>
	<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
	<language>en-us</language>
    
        <atom:link href="https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	
	
	<item>
		<title>My Schedule</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/my_schedule/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 09:58:30 +1000</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/my_schedule/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;I do my best to follow this schedule. Although i usually miss 6am morning classes. 6am at Winter is hard due to the cold. I have my Monday and Wednesday mornings free, so i thought about going to Club de lutas to do 6am classes with them. However this will require me to use a car and be back in time for my mother to use. I am leaning towards not doing this since i would also like to save on fuel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other than this, i work my usual job that is 9am to 5pm. Sometimes i am oncall for work. And when i am oncall, ideally i should not leave the house in case i get called for work outside business hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;monday&#34;&gt;Monday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;boxfit 5:15pm - 6:15pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BJJ at showground: 6:45pm - 8:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Judo at showground: 8:30pm - 10pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tuesday&#34;&gt;Tuesday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exercise: 6am - 7am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BJJ at seven hills: 6:15pm - 7:15pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrestling at seven hills: 7:15pm - 8:15pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wednesday&#34;&gt;Wednesday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;run club: 6:10pm - 7:10pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exercise: 7:10pm - 8:10pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;thursday&#34;&gt;Thursday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exercise: 6am - 7am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exercise: 7am - 8am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exercise: 5:30pm - 6:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exercise: 6:30pm - 7:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;friday&#34;&gt;Friday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exercise: 6am - 7am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BJJ at showground: 6:45pm - 8:30pm + open mat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;saturday&#34;&gt;Saturday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;run club: 7am - 8am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;exercise: 8am - 9am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BJJ at community center: 10:30am - 12pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karate at community center: 12pm - 1:30pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;home: 2pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bikram yoga: 3:30pm - 5pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sunday&#34;&gt;Sunday:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;usually free, but events are usually held on Sunday. This might include running events (city to surf, Marathons, etc) and BJJ tournaments.
There is Bikram Yoga on Sundays too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;resources&#34;&gt;Resources:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://acceler8fitness.com.au/time-table/&#34;&gt;https://acceler8fitness.com.au/time-table/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.clubedelutas.com.au/timetable&#34;&gt;https://www.clubedelutas.com.au/timetable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bkj.net.au/locations-and-times/&#34;&gt;https://www.bkj.net.au/locations-and-times/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>AI_regulation</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/ai_regulation/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 20:50:36 +1000</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/ai_regulation/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;I thought i would put down some of my thoughts upon hearing news about AI regulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what i heard on the news:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Control who gets to create AIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that AIs do not spread misinformation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that AIs and the companies that create AIs follow all rules in regulation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I disagree with this. If anything, it should be enforced that AIs have to be free and open source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If regulation was to go through - what would happen is that a few companies will have total control of the AI market. It would be impossible for one single person to compete in the AI market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will solidify power with those companies that own the AI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead let AI be the wild wild west.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Hogwarts Legacy</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/hogwarts_legacy/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 20:25:38 +1100</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/hogwarts_legacy/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about this game for a while.
This is the type of game that Rebecca would have loved, if she was a gamer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But i am skeptical, and i would like to call it. I don&amp;rsquo;t think this game will be a good game at release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This studio does not have a track record of producing good games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The combat does not look good to me - It is all ranged combat,
It does not look like there is any strategy to the combat.
It does not show any meaningful spacing, guard or timing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have heard people saying this will be on par with Witcher 3 - I disagree with this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will this be game of the year for 2023? I highly doubt it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel a lot of people are expecting this to be an amazing game. It is banking on the Harry Potter nostalgia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>God of war vs marvel</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/god_of_war_vs_marvel/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 11:12:05 +1100</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/god_of_war_vs_marvel/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;This has been on my mind for a while and i decided it would be better if i put it down on paper instead of it staying in my head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On thing i want to compare between the two is the &amp;ldquo;Shield fall&amp;rdquo; stunt.
The idea is that the protagonist falls from a great height and breaks their fall through the use of a shield.
I think it is important to say, the use of a shield in this manner does not break the fall. If you want to break your own fall then i would recommend taking up Judo or BJJ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two stunts below are timestamped&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Captain America doing the stunt in winter soldier: &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/QF38tMQ7HaE?t=152&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/QF38tMQ7HaE?t=152&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kratos doing the stunt in god of war (2018): &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/ea7eWFbncU0?t=321s&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/ea7eWFbncU0?t=321s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the clear winner is god of war. And i am not saying that &amp;ldquo;oh Kratos fall height is greater than Captain America&amp;rsquo;s and therefore it is better.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First thing - Steel beams (They are not steel beams) don&amp;rsquo;t break like that in the way that Marvel has done it. Steel is more elastic than it is brittle. Steel is also better for Tensile rather than compression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Reaction from the stunt is also one thing to consider. Both Protagonists are &amp;ldquo;hurt&amp;rdquo; from the stunt. Yet i feel Kratos gives a way more genuine performance.
(He is a god after all). While Captain America acts like he is really hurt - but then walks it off?
We see the sheer will of Kratos as he looks up to the falling dragon and see&amp;rsquo;s Baldur with his son. Once he knows that they have landed in the center (whats the name of this place?).
He runs towards his target.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also what happens next after the stunt? Both Protagonists &amp;ldquo;move&amp;rdquo; from the area. Captain America is fleeing. While Kratos is running towards a goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The action never stops with god of war. Santa monica have somehow turned krato&amp;rsquo;s running along with his running grunts entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile - Captain America finds a bike (I don&amp;rsquo;t know how) and flees the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;God of war&amp;rsquo;s One camera shot through out the entire game is very technically impressive and a marvel to look to.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Introduction to Hacking</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/introduction-to-hacking/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 16:06:42 +1100</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/introduction-to-hacking/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Hello!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is intended as a Christmas Gift to Jad. However i see no reason as to why it should not be public. At the end of the day, It is just my own ramblings.
However i do think i am qualified to offer some sound advice on the topic of security. After all, i have been working in IT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need to understand that this field will be a life long of learning. You will have to grow/expand your technical toolkit to understand basic things.
Sometimes it will be very frustrating. Fall in love with the process, not the end result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to be technical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In basic terms, you need to understand how the internet works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you will need to understand basic routing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will need to understand how user authentication works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You will need to understand how programs and computers work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And even then, there is no guarantee you will get into Security. But you will have a good chance at getting into IT at the least. So that is a start.
Getting online Certificates increases your chances of getting into IT. CCNA is one example that will help you understand networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember when we had dinner in Canberra i said to you &amp;ldquo;You should learn Linux&amp;rdquo; to which you replied &amp;ldquo;Yeah, everyone has told me to use Linux&amp;rdquo;. But it seems like you don&amp;rsquo;t
know how to start. I think for your first Linux Distro, you should use Ubuntu: &lt;a href=&#34;https://ubuntu.com/download/desktop&#34;&gt;https://ubuntu.com/download/desktop&lt;/a&gt;. It is also easy to install into a machine.
Any YouTube tutorial will do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You could go for Kali Linux, but that is just like any other Linux with a bunch of OpSec tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also hope you enjoy the book i got you (Permanent Record by Edward Snowden). I know i will be purchasing another copy for myself to read through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free Resources you can find on YouTube:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Hated one: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@TheHatedOne&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/@TheHatedOne&lt;/a&gt; This one is a personal favourite of mine. He is not that technical at all and focuses on Privacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LiveOverflow: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@LiveOverflow&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/@LiveOverflow&lt;/a&gt; This channel is a bit technical but it is also very fun.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John Hammond: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@_JohnHammond&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/@_JohnHammond&lt;/a&gt; He is very technical and the videos are very long, but he will show you every step.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Null Byte: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@NullByteWHT&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/@NullByteWHT&lt;/a&gt; Another technical channel but focuses more on tutorial videos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PwnFunction: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@PwnFunction&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/@PwnFunction&lt;/a&gt; Is also tutorial based and focuses on Web security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NetworkChuck: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@NetworkChuck&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/@NetworkChuck&lt;/a&gt; Not really a 100% hacking/security channel but he does have a few videos on the topic. This channel focuses on Networks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DEFCONConference: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@DEFCONConference&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/@DEFCONConference&lt;/a&gt; A Conference on a bunch of hacking talks. They are very enjoyable to watch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mental Outlaw: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@MentalOutlaw&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/@MentalOutlaw&lt;/a&gt; This guy always covers Online trends in the world. He is also a Linux User.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CTFs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OverTheWire: &lt;a href=&#34;https://overthewire.org/wargames/&#34;&gt;https://overthewire.org/wargames/&lt;/a&gt; Start with Bandit and work through the challenges. (All solutions are online and you will learn just by reading through the solutions).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want a more complete list. I found a pretty good resource online: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vitalysim/Awesome-Hacking-Resources&#34;&gt;https://github.com/vitalysim/Awesome-Hacking-Resources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Games</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/games/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 20:44:39 +1100</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/games/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Games i have made&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;spongeswap&#34;&gt;Spongeswap&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am really proud of this one because this is a game that i created without following a tutorial or youtube series. I did this on my own and using free online resources to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used OpenGL and OpenAL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This game was also finished when i left Macquarie cloud services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This game was the birth of the following two tutorials: ThinMatrix and Cross Coast Gaming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/apiotrowski255/SpongeSwap&#34;&gt;https://github.com/apiotrowski255/SpongeSwap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Youtube gameplay:https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GOVHGc2zwcM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;pong&#34;&gt;Pong&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Made in 2023. For this year i will aim to make one game a month. Starting from small simple games and progressively get larger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This short game was made in godot 3.5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Main takeaway from this project (What did i learn?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learnt the difference between reflecting a vector2d and bouncing a vector2d.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What could i do to improve?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like setting the x position of the player paddle every frame is not great. There should be a better way of clamping the paddle on the y axis. However if i did not do this, the ball would apply a force to the player paddle and then it would eventually move out of the screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think when exporting to HTML, i do not need an exit button on the main menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/apiotrowski255/godot-2d-pong&#34;&gt;https://github.com/apiotrowski255/godot-2d-pong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Itch.io link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://awesomea.itch.io/pong&#34;&gt;https://awesomea.itch.io/pong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;breakout&#34;&gt;Breakout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Brick breakers&amp;rdquo;. I thought this project would be easy going in since Breakout is a variation of single player pong. However one challenge i came across is that the ball&amp;rsquo;s code needs to be abstracted. This is because there can be multiple balls in a game scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Issues:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is possible for the ball to be bouncing between the left and right walls infinitely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the is one remaining brick left. It is incredibly hard to hit the last bricks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Github link:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Itch.io link:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;snake&#34;&gt;Snake&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After finishing breakout, i had a choice between two games to work on. Space invaders and Snake. I decided on Snake since it seemed to me to be the harder choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hardest part was getting the blocks to follow each other in a snake like fashion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things to do in future?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allow the snake to tile across the screen (Leave on the left side on the screen and reenter on the right side of the screen.) This i personally find challenging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Github link:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Itch.io link:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Animations</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/animations/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 22:56:47 +1100</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/animations/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;A bunch of animations i have created.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software used:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pivot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe Animate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blender (Current)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Majority of my animations are available on my YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Major works:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;walk-the-walk&#34;&gt;Walk the walk&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A animation for DART1211. This is were i met a good friend &amp;ldquo;Suckerfish&amp;rdquo;. As soon as she mentions Hyun dojo in class, I knew we good pals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apparently i did this in a week? I finished off assignment 1 and handed it in early.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t provide all the animation files for this one because it was broken up to 5 parts and then combined together in Adobe premiere pro.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;slush-invaders-tribute&#34;&gt;Slush invaders tribute&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think with this animation i got a little impatient. I remember i just finished my two year contract with Macquarie cloud services and i was incrediblity burnt out from work.
When i left MCS, i had a goal to finish this animation off. It took longer than expected and i did not want to develop the habit of starting projects and not finishing them.
Gildedguy has seen it and he loved it: Link to his reaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this animation i have also implemented a &amp;ldquo;versioning control&amp;rdquo; type to keep track of my progress and to retain copies/backups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Engagement with this animation was a bit weird - it never went viral, but it had a steady growth. As of writing, it has over nine thousand views (It&amp;rsquo;s pretty close to one million!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adobe animate file:
}} Video can be see here:
}} Adobe file can be downloaded here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;animation-vs-you-the-viewer&#34;&gt;Animation vs You (The Viewer)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A fan animation copying the formula of Animation vs Animator by Alan becker.
I was happy to have shared this with Alan becker - He replied and shared the animation on his facebook page.
I believe the video went viral because soon after Alan released his next video in the series &amp;ldquo;Animation vs YouTube&amp;rdquo;.
This was my first video to surpass one million views. As of writing it has surpassed two million. I doubt it will grow after that.
Video can be see here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lNXHH70fnI4&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lNXHH70fnI4&lt;/a&gt;
Adobe file can be downloaded here: TODO&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;epic-stickfigure-battle---oct-26-2016&#34;&gt;Epic StickFigure Battle - Oct 26 2016&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally this one was going to be named &amp;ldquo;AwesomeA vs Saminator&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;AA vs Saminator&amp;rdquo;. I had a good friend Samitha Balasuriya who i went to high school with.
I thought it would be cool to work on an animation featuring myself and him battling.
I think another part of it was the music. I remember listening to the music and thinking &amp;ldquo;Wow this is cool&amp;rdquo;. I Imagined an epic battle with this music and i guess i brought it to life.
According to my notes - This was done in 3 months
I look back at it now with slight cringe but great fondest.
Youtube link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lXT0qa_SGlA&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lXT0qa_SGlA&lt;/a&gt;
Adobe animate files:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Favourite websites</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/favouritewebsites/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 23:17:48 +1100</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/favouritewebsites/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;A bunch of websites i like with some brief reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lukesmith.xyz/&#34;&gt;https://lukesmith.xyz/&lt;/a&gt; : Luke is the main reason why i have my own website and moving to Hugo (using Lugo)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://stallman.org/&#34;&gt;https://stallman.org/&lt;/a&gt; : The creator of GNU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://linuxtorvalds.com/&#34;&gt;https://linuxtorvalds.com/&lt;/a&gt; : The creator of Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://brendanregg.com/&#34;&gt;https://brendanregg.com/&lt;/a&gt; : For some reason the link does not work. But if you google &amp;ldquo;brendanregg&amp;rdquo; he should be the first result.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://maxzhang.net/&#34;&gt;https://maxzhang.net/&lt;/a&gt; : a get inspiration for me and i love his 3D Art&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ncase.me/&#34;&gt;https://ncase.me/&lt;/a&gt; - Love the idea of explorable explanations and all the other projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blender.org/&#34;&gt;https://blender.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://godotengine.org/&#34;&gt;https://godotengine.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://love2d.org/&#34;&gt;https://love2d.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lua.org/&#34;&gt;https://lua.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ceph.io/&#34;&gt;https://ceph.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lunarvim.org/&#34;&gt;https://www.lunarvim.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open source:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fsf.org/&#34;&gt;https://www.fsf.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;open source books&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://easypeasymethod.org/&#34;&gt;https://easypeasymethod.org/&lt;/a&gt; : I would not say i am out of the woods yet with my pornography addiction, but it has made me realize the biggest stopper is fear.
Furthermore, this was my first time coming across a free and open source book! Its so much more than making money, Its about changing people&amp;rsquo;s lives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Need to add Zlibrary here - Somehow need to find the Onion link.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;blender specific:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blender.org/&#34;&gt;https://blender.org/&lt;/a&gt; - again&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://open3dlab.com/&#34;&gt;https://open3dlab.com/&lt;/a&gt; - A great resource for 3d models, environments and HDRIs. All Free.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://smutba.se/&#34;&gt;https://smutba.se/&lt;/a&gt; - The same as openedlab, except all NSFW&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blendswap.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.blendswap.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wikis:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.installgentoo.com/&#34;&gt;https://wiki.installgentoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://without-systemd.org/&#34;&gt;https://without-systemd.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.osdev.org/&#34;&gt;https://wiki.osdev.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.archlinux.org/&#34;&gt;https://wiki.archlinux.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Musicians:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.daveeddy.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.daveeddy.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.waterflame.com&#34;&gt;https://www.waterflame.com&lt;/a&gt;./ - This guy made pretty much all music for flash games (My childhood).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>About</title>
		<link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/about/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:33:29 +1100</pubDate>
		
		<guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/about/</guid>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Hi my name is Alex and i currently work at &lt;a href=&#34;https://vaultcloud.com.au/&#34;&gt;vault cloud&lt;/a&gt; as a cloud Admin (Customer Technical support)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have graduated from UNSW Sydney with a degree in computer science.
As proof, you can see my &lt;a href=&#34;https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/unsw_degree/testamur.pdf&#34;&gt;Testamur&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/unsw_degree/transcript.pdf&#34;&gt;Transcript&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/unsw_degree/AHEGS.pdf&#34;&gt;AHEGS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am considering continuing my studies at AIE and specialise in Game Programming.
For the longest time, i could always envision myself working as a game programmer.
Right now i do this as a hobby - Self enrolled courses. I mostly use Godot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other option would be to go to Macquarie University for a degree in game development: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mq.edu.au/study/find-a-course/courses/bachelor-of-game-design-and-development&#34;&gt;https://www.mq.edu.au/study/find-a-course/courses/bachelor-of-game-design-and-development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also like animations. I used to work a lot with Adobe animation/flash but ever since they started charging for that as a service, i have been more inclined to
use blender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After reading &lt;a href=&#34;https://manjarno.snorlax.sh/&#34;&gt;https://manjarno.snorlax.sh/&lt;/a&gt; i have switched from Manjaro to Endeavour OS. The main thing Manjaro had going for me was the GUI package manager. And then i came across an issue with OpenSSL, causing me to not being about to update my packages. Therefore i switched to Endeavour. In Future i think i will make the switch to Arch or Artix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things i want to learn (In no particular order):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MongoDB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Terraform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OpenShift&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ansible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ceph&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OpenStack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Networking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NFTables on linux machines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IPsec and SSL VPNs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fortigates - Maybe a few fortinet certificates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ARP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VXLAN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LDAP and OpenLDAP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CCNP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redhat Certificate RHSCA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maybe a few AWS and Azure certificates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoFS and NFS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How Email works&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CheckMK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mattermost deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nextcloud deployment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Svelte and Sveltekit - Frontend development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cable management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hugo : To build this website, i would like to add a navbar and make it look like max zhang&amp;rsquo;s website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;React&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reveal.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wiki.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lock Picking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How Monero and Bitcoin works&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Piano and guitar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unity Engine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unreal engine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Godot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love2d&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Games i like&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bug bumble - N64&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mario Kart - N64&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ratchet and Clank (PS2 - PS3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assassin&amp;rsquo;s creed (1,2,3 - original series)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Halo 3 (xbox 360)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t Escape&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Epic Battle Fantasy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HellTaker - PC (Steam) - Free&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;God of war - PC (Steam) - Paid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Metro Exodus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outer Wilds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt - PC (Steam) - Paid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team Fortress 2 - PC (Steam) - Free&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Armored core 6 - PC (Steam) - Paid&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Film i like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avatar, the last airbender&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Lego Movie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;American Psycho : This film has so many community edits and remixes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blade runner 2049&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Puss in boots 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fight club&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Music i like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anything Touhou. Zun is a great composer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Touhou - The Positive and Negative [ZUN-like Remix] : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JqRu1TfncE4&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JqRu1TfncE4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I imagine this one to be a boss theme - something like a news anchor or pop star (Is this similar to metton from Undertale?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C418 - Aria Math&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I also like Phonk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If i have used the music in an animation - I have to like it. When animating you constantly hear the same music again and again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interesting fact about me: Apparently, when i was really young, i used to watch &amp;ldquo;free willy&amp;rdquo; on repeat continuously. I could not talk at this age but i knew how to work the VHS machine.
Also according to my parents, I could not talk until at the age of four. But hey, I Einstein was a late talker too: &lt;a href=&#34;https://profound-answers.com/did-einstein-really-not-talk-until-he-was-4/&#34;&gt;https://profound-answers.com/did-einstein-really-not-talk-until-he-was-4/&lt;/a&gt;
More on late talkers: &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Late_talker&#34;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Late_talker&lt;/a&gt;
My Mum tells me how worried she was when i was young and not talking. She took me to every Specialist she could see. They did a bunch of tests on me - Made sure i was not deaf.
I think they went on to find nothing. No explanation. I think there were fears that i was Autistic or had a Disability. I am glad to announce that i turned out fine. I am very happy for myself and my family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wonder if i should do a &amp;ldquo;character stats&amp;rdquo; page for myself? Something similar to Cyberpunk character stats? Or Elden Ring?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;body-strength&#34;&gt;Body (Strength)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My weight: 102KG, (Now it is 97KG, Measured on 7th of August 2023)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My Height: 185cm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Max DeadLift: 90KG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Max brench press: 60KG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;body-stamina&#34;&gt;Body (Stamina)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beep test: 8.2 - Tested on 17th of May 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10km run in 59 minutes. - Achieved on 7th of May 2023 (Sydney 10)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;14km run in 1:22:56 (1 hour, 22 minutes and 56 seconds). - Achieved on 13th of August 2023 (City 2 surf)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;21km run in 2:21:41 (2 hours, 21 minutes and 41 seconds). - Achieved on 21st of May 2023 (Hoka half marathon)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;body-other&#34;&gt;Body (other)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blood type: B+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eye sight: ?? (I wear glasses)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yoga: Postures i can do:
Touch toes? (Hopefully one day but not right now (22nd of Dec))&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reflexes
BBJ? Karate, Muay Thai.
Floro knife defense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technical Ability (Which in today&amp;rsquo;s world is the same as Intelligence?)
CCNA
RHSCA (Not today, but aiming for it.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cool&#34;&gt;Cool&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current Youtube following: 10K&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github followers: 10&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://socialblade.com/youtube/c/alexpiotrowski/realtime&#34;&gt;https://socialblade.com/youtube/c/alexpiotrowski/realtime&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(Not that it really matters to be honest)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>
