<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Piotrowski</title>
    <link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alex Piotrowski</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:33:29 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Games</title>
      <link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 20:44:39 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/games/</guid>
      <description>Games i have made
Spongeswap
I am really proud of this one because this is a game that i created without following a tutorial or youtube series. I did this on my own and using free online resources to do so.
Used OpenGL and OpenAL This game was also finished when i left Macquarie cloud services This game was the birth of the following two tutorials: ThinMatrix and Cross Coast Gaming Github link: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animations</title>
      <link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 22:56:47 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/animations/</guid>
      <description>A bunch of animations i have created.
Software used:
Pivot Adobe Animate Blender (Current) The Majority of my animations are available on my YouTube.
Major works:
Walk the walk
A animation for DART1211. This is were i met a good friend &amp;ldquo;Suckerfish&amp;rdquo;. As soon as she mentions Hyun dojo in class, I knew we good pals. Apparently i did this in a week? I finished off assignment 1 and handed it in early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favourite websites</title>
      <link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/favouritewebsites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 23:17:48 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/favouritewebsites/</guid>
      <description>A bunch of websites i like with some brief reasons. People:
https://lukesmith.xyz/ : Luke is the main reason why i have my own website and moving to Hugo (using Lugo) https://stallman.org/ : The creator of GNU https://linuxtorvalds.com/ : The creator of Linux https://brendanregg.com/ : For some reason the link does not work. But if you google &amp;ldquo;brendanregg&amp;rdquo; he should be the first result. https://maxzhang.net/ : a get inspiration for me and i love his 3D Art Software:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:33:29 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexpiotrowski.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi my name is Alex and i currently work at vault cloud as a cloud Admin (Customer support)
I have graduated from UNSW Sydney with a degree in computer science. As proof, you can see my Testamur, Transcript and AHEGS.
I am considering continuing my studies at AIE and specialise in Game Programming.
test: test
I am currently running on Manjaro Distro but i am considering switching to debian: https://manjarno.snorlax.sh/ Sure debian might be slower with the updates but it is stable as hell.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
